[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What female musician won five Grammy Awards for her album and song Back to Black?", "correct_answer": "Amy Winehouse", "incorrect_answers": ["Beyonce Knowles", "Christina Aguilera", "Alicia Keys"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What medical condition is the chlorella algae beneficial for?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["High cholesterol levels", "Radiation exposure", "High blood pressure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This astronomical term refers to the outermost layer of the sun, which is a low density cloud of plasma, with higher transparency than the inner layers.", "correct_answer": "Corona", "incorrect_answers": ["Chromosphere", "Photosphere", "Solar Wind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ghosts have taken a significant place in literature and art since this period.", "correct_answer": "Renaissance", "incorrect_answers": ["Middle Ages", "Romanticism", "Baroque"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it believed that Smilodon was a social animal?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Nickel?", "correct_answer": "Ni", "incorrect_answers": ["N", "Nc", "Nk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Japanese car brand is also a word in Spanish?", "correct_answer": "Honda", "incorrect_answers": ["Toyota", "Nissan", "Mazda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of these animals hibernate. Which one does not?", "correct_answer": "Sloth", "incorrect_answers": ["Mouse", "Frog", "Snake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie, The African Queen, how did Charlie and Rose plan to destroy the German war boat on the lake?", "correct_answer": "Build homemade torpedoes and ram the war boat.", "incorrect_answers": ["Make firebombs and torch the boat.", "Ram the boat and puncture the hull.", "Sneak aboard and set off an explosive charge."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the doctor writes, CNs 2-12 intact, which of the following would be true?", "correct_answer": "The patient is able to close and open the eyes.", "incorrect_answers": ["The patient is a man.", "The cervical nerves are all functioning normally.", "All of the lymph nodes in the cervical chain are normal."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Olive oil lowers total cholesterol and LDL levels in the blood.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the term blood serum refer to?", "correct_answer": "Blood plasma without the clotting proteins", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Blood without the cell elements", "It is a synonym for blood plasma."]}]